splashnews.com 2017-12-12

# Splash News

**Splash News Privacy Policy**

Effective date: December 13, 2016

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of Splash News and Picture Agency, LLC, its business divisions and its corporate affiliates (collectively, "Company" or "us" or "we") with regard to the web sites, online services, and applications, including mobile applications, that display or link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Services") and that are operated by or on behalf of Company.

Please note that by agreeing to this Privacy Policy and providing your personal information you consent to:

  * the use of your personal information by Company for the uses identified below in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of information about you to servers located both within and outside the United States, as necessary.

  1. **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Company collects certain personal information from users of these Services. To create user accounts, authorized users must provide certain contact and account information such as name, email address, billing address, and phone number in order to access, license and download images and content, and use Services. Company may use certain account information such as credit or debit card number and company information of authorized users to conduct credit inquiries. Company may use this information about you that it collects for the following purposes:

  * to process your order and any invoices;
  * to maintain or update your Company account;
  * to send you updates about special offers, new services, special promotions, and noteworthy news and events;
  * to fulfill the terms of a promotion or contest;
  * to fulfill a service to you, for example, if you choose to submit content to the Services, we may use your personal information to respond to your submission;
  * to contact you in response to forms such as "Contact Us" or Live Chat or emailed requests;
  * to contact you about a material change to this Privacy Policy or Site Usage Agreement, if necessary;
  * to comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on us; and
  * to third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process, including, but not limited to mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets.

Company may also share or disclose your personal information that is collected in the Services to its parent and affiliated companies who require your personal information for research, administrative and/or internal business purposes. These parties may use such information to contact you with an advertisement or offering related to a product or services.

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, Company does not sell, share or rent information about its customers to third parties for their marketing or promotional purposes.

Certain Services may enable use with certain social network services. To the extent you are required to log in to a social network services to utilize features of the Services, Company may receive information about you from such social network services, including your login and settings, and you authorize us to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information available to us through such social network services. Please be aware that your actions may also subject to the privacy policies and various terms of service applicable to such social network services.

We may also disclose your personal information: to comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request; to enforce or apply our Site Usage Terms, content license agreements, contributor agreements, or other agreements existing between us, including for billing and collection purposes; and if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our customers or others, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  2. **DATA RETENTION**

We will retain information about you for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use information about you to provide you services contact us at sales@splashnews.com. We will retain and use information about you as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  3. **LIGHTBOX REFERRAL**

If you use our referral service for informing a friend about our Services, or inviting a friend to view your lightbox, we will ask you for the friend's name and email address. Company will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Services. Company does not retain this information.

  4. **PROFILE INFORMATION**

Your profile information (such as company type and language preference) in the registration form is used by Company to create personalized content, services, and advertising in the Services. Company may also profile your Services activity in order to accurately track your account and provide you with Company products and services that correspond to your interests. Company may also compile data in aggregate form so that we may better understand the users that are visiting our Services. For example, we may produce reports on the most popular search terms by collecting general search term data based on individual searches. Aggregate data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies a user. Company may provide or enable access to non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our Services users to third parties for their audit, research and analytical purposes.

  5. **AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION / MOBILE AND DEVICES**

As is true of most services, when you access and use the Services, we gather certain information automatically. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. Depending on the Services, we may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access the Services, such as geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser language and other transactional information.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Services, to track users' movements around the Services and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

If you are logged into your user account, we are able to link this automatically collected data to such account, including sales history. IP addresses are tied to geographic information to segregate customer location for analytical purposes.

  6. **USE OF SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We occasionally hire or partner with other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as managing and handling the processing and delivery of mailings (both email and postal mail) and marketing, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our Services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of information about you and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

  7. **CHANGE OF ADDRESS OR CONTACT INFORMATION**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, you may correct, update, or delete inaccuracies in information about you by making the change through the "Customer Service" page of our Services, by emailing our Customer Support at sales@splashnews.com, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Your request will be responded to within thirty (30) days. We may not be able to delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account, and we may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

  8. **SECURITY**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Services like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to or through our Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in the Services.

  9. **COOKIES AND PIXEL TAGS**

When you use the Services, Company sends your computer a cookie, which is a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and contains non-personal information about the user. Cookies only identify the user's computer. Cookies allow Company to make its Services more useful by storing information about your preferences. For example, Company will send your computer a cookie to maintain default settings such as your language preference. You can set your browser's options not to accept cookies, but this may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the Services. For more about the types and individual cookies used by the Services, see our Cookie Policy.

Company uses a third party to assist in managing the licensing of our images. This third party uses clear GIFs, a tiny 1x1 pixel GIF, to digitally watermark our images, in both a visible and invisible manner. When you purchase a licensed image from us, the visible watermark is then removed from the image, however, in certain lower resolution images, an invisible watermark may remain, allowing Company and the third party to track certain usage of such images on the Internet.

We use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our websites and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our websites and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us. We also work with third-party companies, including Google, that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having your information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

  10. **COMMUNICATIONS AND CHOICE**

Company does not rent, share or sell email lists to third parties for their promotional purposes. Company may send you email to notify you about your recent order, to respond to your inquiries or requests, or to otherwise provide or request information concerning your account. Such emails will be sent to the email address you provide to Company.

Company offers its members the choice to not receive emails or updates about special benefits, promotions, or offers from Company. If you no longer wish to receive these updates, or you wish to unsubscribe from your Company account please complete the Contact Us form in the Services and let us know in the comments section that you would like to be removed from the mailing list.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication (e.g. following the unsubscribe instructions within the email) or you may contact us at sales@splashnews.com, or telephone us at 1-310-342-1500, to opt out.

  11. **SURVEYS, PROMOTIONS, AND CONTESTS**

Participation in surveys, promotions, or contests in the Services is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personal information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award promotional gifts prizes and may be retained and used by Company to otherwise provide Services to you. Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use of the Services.

  12. **DISCUSSION THREADS**

Company may offer discussion threads and comment boxes in the Services. If you use Company's discussion threads or comment boxes, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these discussion threads. To request removal of your personal information from our discussion threads, contact us at sales@splashnews.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information.

  13. **LINKS**

Please be aware that the Services may contain links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and we encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site. We recommend that our users read the privacy policies of each and every service that collects personal information.

  14. **CHILDREN**

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use these Services unsupervised and we ask that children do not register for an account or submit any personal information to us. By using these Services unsupervised, and/or registering for an account, you warrant that you are 18 years of age or older.

  15. **CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to make any material changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Services including the home page and other places we deem appropriate, prior to implementing the change so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Continuing to use the Services after such changes constitute your acceptance and consent to the updated terms of our Privacy Policy.

  16. **SAFE HARBOR**

Company complies with the U.S.–E.U. and U.S.–Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Company has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Company's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Company commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Customer Service at sales@splashnews.com or 1-310-342-1500. Company has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

  17. **QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to Company, please contact Customer Service at sales@splashnews.com: or call 1-310-342-1500. You may also write to us at the address listed below:

Splash News and Picture Agency, LLC  
15250 Ventura Blvd, Suite 300  
Sherman Oaks, CA 91403
